I am live? Okay. We shall see if this works. Hi, good morning. I'm going to set up my power chat link. It should be set up for media. So any song you want to suggest or put on, you know, we'll play. Hi, babe. We'll see if it works. Okay. I'm going to ask you to do a test.
test the message to see if it's coming up on the screen got my here's how you do
it guys hi guys okay so I need to get to my chat okay there I am okay it is
$3 and up for messages between five or five dollars and up for a message and
Okay, okay, and wants to test it out. I'm gonna try to test it too. I'll set up a night walk to man, too
Okay, and we'll see if this works. I don't know. I don't know if it's working. Yeah, it's nice dream cute
How are we doing? There we go. The link is pinned. Hi
Be the first
Be the first to send one
Okay, well, how are you? Like how was last night? I think last night was pretty awesome. We had a pretty good night last night
We had mini Manson in the show around the show. That was so cool. Hi, babe
16 for current viewers reviews interesting. Okay. Hi, babe. Oh
I have my coffee. I have a coffee this morning. Okay, I think it's sending a test. So we'll see if it works
Okay, let me know guys if you see anything pop up
I'm trying to like get this working. It has kind of complicated stuff. It's like yeah, just do it through a couple things
I don't have this not on the streamer right now
Doing it. I don't know if I can even see my chats right now
But I see like certain things like I see people on the screen. I don't know this is the test. Hi
There's miss Lola
Hi, Lola. Oh
So cute
So cute. So if you guys if you see anything on the screen pop them on the screen like let me know
I don't know. I don't see anything yet, but we shall see
Okay, I guess I said that I'm gonna have an excellent
Studio going though. That's good. Excellent. Okay
Okay, no one's talking yet. Just even talking shout out to me. I don't know. I can see the chats now
So there we go that I can program in my my nightbot to start working
You guys want to play with a nightbot you can too
There's some fun stuff
Okay, so with the TTS
You know why it's fun. It's because
You can't say anything you want to me on that like
Hey, 20 you're doing lawn work. You'll be in and out of breaks. Okay good. Good to see you. Thanks for talking 2020
I'm good to see you
Yeah, um, so we're seeing what happens so many Manson was a good guy a great guy, you know, I love
mini manson as a guest and uh also like you know short show royalty you know way because
mini manson has it was on about a year ago but i was really happy to made a little documentary
a mini mini manson documentary right it was short like 10 minutes but it was all based on
information from our our uh our interview last year oh you oh what are you doing lola oh yeah i
Which is very calm. Okay, so hey grateful. How are you? Good to see you. I was testing at this TTS thing
I don't know. It's like um, like if you people want to play a song or people want to
Have a message, but and I'm just trying to test to make sure it works
And I'm not 100% sure you have a new video on top. It's crystal. Okay
Okay, I might have to
See I might have to just restart it so I can like do the
so I can do
My have my stream yard. So this will have to well to put on the back burner for just a little bit
I'm gonna get this working perfectly
This was a test. I'm gonna start right back on
By my new channel. We're gonna play great pulls. Um
We're gonna play great pulls video on crystal. Okay, just find the next find the extreme. I love you. I'll be right back
People okay